http://www.payless.com/privacy-policy

flag-costa-rica
Free Standard Shipping + Use coupon code 12DAYS for an additional 30% off.WomenAthleticsRunningCanvasFashionSandalsFlip FlopsFlatsWedgesSlidesSlip-onCasualsFlatsBoatOxford & LoaferCanvasSlip OnDressPumps & HeelsWedgesBootsAnkle BootsTall BootsDanceSafe-T-StepMenAthleticsRunningCanvasFashionLace upSandalsSlip-onSlidesFlip FlopCasualsOxford & LoaferSlip-onBootsHikerWorkbootsSafe-T-StepGirlsAthleticsCanvasFashionRunningSandalsSlip OnFashionFlip FlopsSlidesCasualsFlatsWedgesFashionCanvasOxford & LoaferMary JaneDressSpecial OccasionMary JaneDanceBoysAthleticsRunningCanvasFashionSandalsSlip OnFlip FlopsCasualsBoatCanvasOxford & LoaferDressBootsWesternAccessoriesHandbagsMaskBrandsAerosolesAiratorsAirwalkAmerican EagleBrashComfort Plus By PredictionsCross TrekkersDeflex By DexterDisneyFioniK-SwissKendall + KylieLA GearLower East SideMarvel EntertainmentMonster JamNickelodeonPredictionsRugged OutbackSafe-T-StepSmartFitSpotlightsTeeny ToesZoe & ZacStyles Under $20USAUSAEcuadorColombiaCosta RicaGuatemalaPhilipinesUnited Arab EmiratesSaudi ArabiaIngresar4 days left to receive your standard shipped package by December 25th!PAYLESS PRIVACY POLICYAs described in this Privacy Policy, Payless values our customers and respects their privacy. By visiting any part of our web sites (the 'site'), you consent to the policies and practices described in this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Service of our sites, which are incorporated herein by reference.INTRODUCTIONIn this policy we use 'we' to mean Payless ShoeSource Worldwide, LLC. This Privacy Policy describes how we process your personal information as you use our website located at https://payless.com/ and while you shop in one of our stores, use our mobile app, as well as use any services, tools, technology, products, and features (together, the “Services”) provided, operated or owned by Payless ShoeSource Worldwide, LLC. We collect information from our interactions with you, other customers and other parties to help us provide an enhanced shopping experience and for a variety of other business purposes. We seek to provide products, services, and valuable offers to you and your family through the information gathered. We secure your information to ensure confidentiality and integrity of your data. We offer you certain choices about the way your personal information is collected and used. If you have any questions or comments about any content please contact us.As described in this Privacy Policy, we share your personal information with our affiliates, third party service providers, and business partners, among other types of sharing. Please see below for the full Policy details or use the quick links above for specific topics.We may modify this Policy at any time, without prior notice, and changes may apply to any personal information we already hold about you, as well as any new Personal Information collected after the Policy is modified. If we make changes, we will notify you by revising the date at the bottom of this Policy. We will provide you with advanced notice if we make any material changes to how we collect, use or disclose your personal information or that impact your rights under this Policy. If you continue to access or use our Services after receiving the notice of changes, you acknowledge your acceptance of the updated Policy.In addition, we may provide you with real time disclosures or additional information about the data handling practices of specific parts of our Services. Such notices may supplement this Policy or provide you with additional choices about how we process your Personal Information.INFORMATION WE COLLECT FROM YOUWhen you use our Services, we collect personal information such as: Contact information. Such as your name, postal address, phone number, email, and birth month and year. Profile and account information. This may include your contact information, payment information, account password, shopping and product preferences, and other information about your user account. Social media information. This may include your social media handle, photos, or other media you share online and share with us. Payment information. This may include your payment method and information and billing address. Browsing and device information. This may include information about your online activity and device such as and not limited to your phone, tablet, or laptop. Such information may include IP address, cookie identifiers, and unique identifiers. Please refer to the “Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies” section below for more information Geolocation information. Please refer to “Geo-Location Data” section below for more information. Size and preference information. From time to time, we may develop and use certain technologies (such as cameras or screeners) that may help assess your shoe size or other information about your shoe preferences.We also maintain a record of your product interests and the purchases you make through our Services. You may also provide personal information when you post reviews, send us feedback or provide other user generated content at our site or sites on which we have a presence. We may from time to time use your postings or reviews to be placed on other areas of our site or repost social media content you post.You may choose not to provide certain information but choosing to do so may prevent you from being able to take advantage of many of Payless' programs.When you use the Services, we automatically collect information about the Services you use and how you use them (including IP address, browser type, device ID), as described below. Service Data:
We collect information about your interactions with the Services, such as the pages or other content you view, and other actions you perform while using the Services. Log Data: We automatically collect log information when you use the Services. This might include your IP address, access times, hardware and software information, device information, device event information (e.g. crashes, unsuccessful logins, browser type), the web page you’ve viewed or engaged with before or after using the Services, and other relevant information. Cookies and Similar Tracking Technologies: We may use various tracking technologies to collect and store information about your use of our Services. We use these tools to ensure that you receive a personalized experience, to provide you with certain functions on our Services, to keep your account safe, and to improve and optimize our Services. Please refer to the “Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies” section below for more information.APPLYING FOR A JOBIf you apply to work with us, we will use the information you supply to process your application and to gather recruitment statistics. Payless may transfer your information outside of your home country and to other companies during the application process. Your personal information will be maintained in accordance with our records retention guidelines. If you have any questions please contact us.HOW WE COLLECT ADDITIONAL INFORMATIONWe may collect additional information about you from our joint marketing partners or from unrelated third parties. For example, we may collect demographic & behavioral information, and we may use mailing lists from third parties.COOKIES AND OTHER TRACKING TECHNOLOGYWe use computer cookies and other tracking technology such as web beacons, pixels, and tags (collectively “cookies”) to make your shopping experience more efficient, convenient and personalized. By using the site, you consent to our use of cookies. Cookies are small files, typically comprised of letters and numbers, that your computer or mobile device saves when you visit certain websites. When you return to the websites that save cookies on your device—or visit other websites that use the same cookies—the websites recognize such cookies and your browsing device. Generally, we use first-party and third-party cookies for the following purposes: To make our Services function properly; To provide a secure browsing experience during your use of our Services; To collect information about your use of our Services to help us improve and optimize our Services and market to you; To remember your preferences for your convenience.This data may also be used in communications but we do not identify individuals in these communications.You can enable, disable, or delete cookies through the browser you are using to access our Services. To do this, follow the instructions provided by your browser (usually located within the “Help”, “Tools” or “Edit” settings). Please note, if you set your browser to disable cookies, you may not be able to access secure areas of our Services, and/or parts of the Services may not work properly for you. You can find more information about how to change your browser cookie settings at https://www.allaboutcookies.org.GOOGLE ANALYTICSWe use Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. ('Google') to collect certain information relating to your use of the Services. Google Analytics uses cookies and other forms of tracking technology. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage.Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google's behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website.By using this website, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above. For more information regarding Google Analytics please visit Google's website, and pages that describe Google Analytics, such as www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html.IN-STORE CAMERASWe use in-store cameras or other screening technology for security and operational purposes.GEO-LOCATION DATAWe may capture and record certain information regarding your location and use (also known as 'Geo-Location' or 'Location-Data') through your store purchase and online or mobile site interactions. This allows us to provide you with the services or functionality offered by our programs.We may link your Geo-Location to other information that you provide to us or that may be accessed in connection with your use of our Services. Our ability to offer certain functionality through our online or mobile application is based on your use and acceptance, which may include associated information to third-parties. Please reference our Terms of Service for more information on the use of our specific programs.ADVERTISING & DO NOT TRACK MECHANISMSWe may use information about how you browse and shop in order to show you advertisements that are more relevant to your interests. We may use cookies and other information to provide relevant interest-based advertising to you. Interest-based ads are ads presented to you based on your browsing behavior in order to provide you with ads more tailored to your interests. These interest-based ads may be presented to you while you are browsing our site or third-party sites not owned by us. To learn more about interest-based advertisements visit the Digital Advertising Alliance and the Network Advertising Initiative websites (www.aboutads.info and www.networkadvertising.org).What is 'Do Not Track'? Do Not Track (DNT) is a privacy preference that users can set in their web browsers. DNT is a simple way for users to inform websites that they do not want certain information to be collected.When you turn on DNT in your browser, we no longer have visibility to the sites you visit after you have left Payless.com. We still know the site you were visiting immediately before you came to Payless.com and we will continue to track the parts of our site which you visit, including information about your checkout. However, when you turn on DNT in your browser, we stop collecting information about your recent visits to websites that have integrated our buttons or widgets. We stop collecting the unique browser cookie that links your browser to visits to these websites for tailoring suggestions or ads.DATA COLLECTION BY THIRD PARTIESWe may collect your information from third party companies. These third parties may collect personal information in variety of ways; we may partner with them to collect information about you, utilize them in order to collect information directly from you, or otherwise access personal information through them. For example, we may use a third party to place advertising on other online sites. These advertising companies collect information about your visits to our site or interaction with our email through the use of tracking tools such as tags, pixel tracking and cookies, and your online activity at other sites.These tools allow them to use information about your visits to help us serve you better. We also use web beacons to review how visitors navigate our site or interact with our email advertising. If you would like more information about this practice, and your choices and they relate to this practice, please contact us.HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATIONOur primary purpose for collecting personal information is for us to provide you with a secure, efficient and beneficial shopping experience.We may use your personal information for orders to: process and fulfill an order notify you of order status verify information about you and your orderWe may contact you if we have questions regarding your order or purchase through email, phone or postal mail. Additionally, we may use your personal information for marketing purposes to: improve services and content customize advertising inform you about future: promotional offers for our goods as well as other goods and services you might be interested in,special sales,new products,special program offers, and service updates. communicate preferences you have indicated any other purpose disclosed at the point of collectionThese communications may be sent via email, postal mail, text message, or through a mobile application dependent upon your preferences. Unless by local provincial law you are required to opt-in, you always have the choice to opt-out of receiving these marketing communications.We may use your information to provide services and customer support that you may request, as well as to correct problems, resolve disputes and collect fees.We may also use the information we collect as necessary to comply with legal requirements, to enforce the site Terms of Service, to prevent fraud, to co-operate with law enforcement and regulatory authorities and to stop other prohibited, illegal or harmful activities.PROMOTIONAL PARTICIPATIONWe may use your personal information to contact you if you participate in a sweepstakes, contest or promotion. This includes promotions on-line, over the phone, through a mobile application, on social media, or at one of our stores. Contact may occur via email, postal mail, telephone, text message, a social media platform, or through a mobile application regarding our products, services, contests and promotions. You may choose at any time not to receive these marketing communications. We may still need to contact you on a limited basis, however - for example, to notify winners and to fulfill promotional obligations.WHO WE SHARE YOUR DATA WITHPAYLESS FAMILY AND AFFILIATESWe share information across Payless family of brands and companies and we may use servers and resources of other members of the group to process your data. Our main servers are in Topeka, Kansas, USA and it is likely that your data will be held on servers there and at other Payless locations around the world. By using and accessing our site, residents and citizens of countries and jurisdictions outside of the United States agree and consent to the transfer to and processing of personal information on servers located in the United States, and that the protection of such information may be different than required under the laws of your residence or location.MERGERS & ACQUISITIONSIf we sell or buy any business (in whole or in part) or any assets, we may disclose your personal information to the buyers of the business and their advisors. If Payless or some of its assets are acquired by a third party, the data held will be one of the transferred assets. Similarly, your personal information may be passed on to a successor in interest in the event of a reorganization, reconstruction, liquidation, bankruptcy or administration. It may be that any buyer or successor buys all or only part of our business. It may also be the case that they are not in the same line of business as us.THIRD PARTY SERVICE PROVIDERSWe may combine your information with information we collect from other companies (such as demographic or behavioral data) for a variety of purposes, including to improve and personalize our services to you. We may also use third-party companies to assist in collection and analysis of data.We may share your information with companies employed outside of Payless that perform services specifically for Payless. For example, we may retain an outside company to create and distribute a direct mail or email offering. They may sometimes have access to information collected by us, including your personal information, in the course of providing products or services to us. In those situations, the outside company is performing work for Payless, and we take appropriate steps to ensure that your personal information is used only to provide the services requested by us.We may also disclose that personal information to third-parties to whom you explicitly ask us to send your information.BUSINESS PARTNERSWe may collect, share, or sell personal information with independent, unaffiliated third-parties for any purpose. These third parties include marketing consultants, advertisers, advertising technology platforms, and data preparation companies, data brokers, and any other organization. Third parties may combine your personal information with data collected across the internet or from other sites. Once shared, this information may be used for a variety of purposes outside of our control or direction.If you have an issues or questions in regards to your information, you can contact us to opt-out at Customer.Service@payless.com.LEGAL REQUIREMENTS & COMPLIANCEWe reserve the right to release account and other personal information about you when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, in response to legal process and law enforcement requests, to enforce or apply our Terms of Service and other agreements, or to protect our rights, property, safety or other interests those of our parent company, affiliates and shareholders, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.SECURITYSAFEGUARDING OF YOUR INFORMATIONWe endeavor to protect your information against unauthorized disclosures whether in our stores, in a program or site by: trying to limit access to people who need the information to do their jobs informing Payless employees and third parties about their responsibility to adhere to our own business ethical standards and confidentiality policies regularly monitor our systems for possible vulnerabilities and attacksWe place physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to secure the confidentiality and integrity of the personal information we collect and ensure to prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, ensure correct use of personal information.These safeguards are designed to protect against, but are not a guarantee against, the loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction of personal information.We use HTTPS, also known as SSL encryption, to transfer information securely from your web browser to our web servers. This means that all of your personal information, including your credit or debit card number, is encrypted when transferred through our Service to avoid the decoding of that information by anyone other than us.However, no technology is 100% secure, where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our programs or sites, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone and take reasonable steps for protecting your information.HOW WE PROTECT KIDS' PRIVACY ON-LINEOur site and our service is general audience and it is our intention that our site and service should be used only by persons over age 13. Any feature, tool, or technology developed or used by Payless is intended for use only by persons over age 13. We are concerned about the safety of children when they use the Internet and will never knowingly request personal information from anyone under the age of 13. If the parent or guardian of a child under 13 believes that the child has provided us with any personal data, the parent or guardian of that child should contact our Customer Service Center and ask to have this personal information deleted from our files. If we otherwise obtain knowledge that we have personal information about a child under 13 in our files, we will delete that personal information from our existing files so that it is not in retrievable form.LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES AND SERVICESOur sites may contain links to other sites. You should review the policies of those sites before providing any personal information, as we do not control their privacy policies or practices. Our sites provide links solely for the convenience and information of our customers.YOUR CHOICESWe provide you with reasonable access to your personal information to update and manage. If you would like to update your information at the: Store - An associate can assist you with the updates and choices to update or change your:Personal information (name, address, etc.) email address delivery of: emails or home mailings
Online - Login to your account at https://www.payless.com/account where you may choose to update or change your: Personal information (name, address, etc.) email address password payment methods
Mobile App - For questions on the app, please contact us to assist you. If you have an issues or questions in regards to your information or choices, you can contact us to have it corrected, amended or opt-out.PUBLICLY-SHARED INFORMATIONAny information you have shared on another website (Facebook, Instagram, YouTube, Twitter, Pinterest, etc.) may become public information. We cannot control the use of information disclosed in public forums, such as forums, bulletin boards, blogs, chat rooms, and networking functions. You should exercise caution when disclosing information in these public areas and be careful how you disclose your personal information or information related to you.Content posted in public areas, including advice and opinions, represents the views and is the responsibility of those who post the content. We do not necessarily endorse, support, verify, or agree with the content posted. If you have any questions or comments about any such content, please send us an email at Customer.Service@payless.comIf you have an issues or questions in regards to your information or choices, you can contact us to have it corrected, amended or opt-out.OPTING OUTIf you receive home mailings, promotional emails, marketing communications, text messages or other communications from us and you wish to stop receiving you may opt out through one of the following: Store associate will update upon request Online clicking 'Unsubscribe' at the bottom of an email you receive from us Mobile App removing the app from your device will opt you out Messaging You may opt-out at any time by following the instructions provided in the email or SMS/MMS message. You may always contact us at customer.service@payless.com to opt-out. If you ask us to remove your information from our list, we will maintain your name in a 'do not contact' file to ensure we can honor your request. Depending on what programs you are enrolled in it may require additional opting out. It can take up to 10 days to process your email or text message request, and 6-8 weeks to process your postal mail request, during which you may continue to receive communications from us. If you are concerned that we have not acted in accordance with our privacy policy please contact privacy@payless.com.NOTICE TO CALIFORNIA RESIDENTSThis section only applies to individuals who are residents of California under the California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018 (“CCPA”) and other California privacy laws (together “California Laws”). Personal Information Collected Payless collects the following categories of personal information, as defined by California Laws: Inferences; Identifiers; Categories of personal information related to the California Customer Records statute (Cal. Civ. Code § 1798.80); Geolocation Data; Internet Activity; and Commercial InformationWe collect them for the purposes described above, and may share as outlined the section titled, “Who We Share Your Data With” above.California Residents Rights Under California Laws, California residents have the following rights (“Rights”) listed below. Your Right to Access and Right to Deletion are not absolute and are subject to certain exceptions. For instance, we cannot disclose specific pieces of personal information if the disclosure would create a substantial, articulable, and unreasonable risk to the security of the Personal Information, your account with us or the security of the business’s systems of networks Disclosure & Access Rights: California residents have the right to request in writing from a business, (i) a list of the categories of personal information, such as name, address, e–mail address, and the type of services provided to the customer, that a business has disclosed to third parties (including Independent Affiliates that are separate legal entities) during the immediately preceding calendar year for the third parties' direct marketing purposes, and (ii) the names and addresses of all such third parties. In addition, California residents have the right to request that we disclose to them (i) the categories of personal information we have collected about them, (ii) the categories of sources from which personal information is collected, (iii) the business or commercial purpose for the information collection, (iv) the categories of third parties with whom we have shared personal information, and (v) the specific pieces of personal information we hold about an individual. Deletion Rights: California residents have the right to have their personal information deleted, unless the personal information is necessary for Payless or our service provider to: complete a transaction for which the personal information was collected, provide a good or service requested by the consumer or otherwise perform a contract between the business and the consumer; detect security incidents; protect against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent or illegal activity (or prosecute those responsible); debug to identify and repair functionality errors; exercise or ensure the right of another to exercise free speech or another legal right; comply with the California Electronic Communications Privacy Act, which compels the production of or access to electronic communication information or electronic device information with a search warrant; engage in research in the public interest (if the consumer has provided informed consent); to enable solely internal uses aligned with the consumer's expectations given their relationship with the business; comply with a legal obligation; otherwise use the information internally in a lawful manner compatible with the context in which the consumer provided it. Do Not Sell: Californian residents have the right to opt-out of having their personal information sold. In the proceeding twelve months, we may have transferred personal information in a manner that would be considered a sale under California Laws.Californians can exercise their privacy rights by contacting us at Customer.Service@payless.com.Response Time.
We will handle request under Applicable Law in California. When a request is made, we may verify your identity to protect your privacy and security. We will respond to written rights requests within 45 days following receipt at the e–mail or mailing address stated above.HOW TO CONTACT USFor any questions, concerns or other request please contact us by: Email: Customer.Service@payless.com. Mail: Payless ShoeSource Customer Service 4910 Corporate Centre Drive, Suite 210 Lawrence, Kansas 66047To protect your privacy and security, we may ask you to verify your identity and/or provide other details to help us respond to your request before granting access or making corrections. Please note that any requests to update your personal information may take up to 10 days for your email request, and 6-8 weeks to process your postal mail request.AMENDMENTS TO OUR PRIVACY POLICYWe reserve the right to change our Privacy Policy as our business changes. If our policy changes in the future, we will post an updated privacy policy on our Website. You can tell if this policy has changed by checking the revision date that appears at the end of this policy. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here that it has been updated, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we use and/or disclose it. Continued use of our services or systems after we publish or communicate a notice about any changes to this Privacy Policy means that you are consenting to the changes. If you would like a permanent record of this Privacy Policy please print a copy. Last updated on August 21, 2020.SIGN UP TO GET A 10% DISCOUNTSign upCORPORATE INFOAbout usCareersCUSTOMER SERVICEContact usOrder statusShipping / ReturnsTerms of servicePrivacy PolicyFAQSHOPWomenMenGirlsBoysMy accountFind your fit+WomensMensKids
